[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This chemical is found in the venom of most ants and some other insects.", "correct_answer": "Formic acid", "incorrect_answers": ["Formaldehyde", "Saxitoxin", "Cyanic acid"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many teeth does an average human have?", "correct_answer": "32", "incorrect_answers": ["28", "29", "34"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "William Friedkin began his directorial career doing documentaries and live TV shows. He won several awards for this documentary about a death-row inmate.", "correct_answer": "The People vs. Paul Crump", "incorrect_answers": ["Retribution", "A Measured Life", "An Execution"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Where does Fezzik carry Buttercup, Vizzini and Inigo up a rope in the film The Princess Bride?", "correct_answer": "The Cliffs of insanity", "incorrect_answers": ["The Precipice of Death", "The Cliffs of Despair", "The Precipice of Peril"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Rowan Atkinson is know for his over-articulation of the sound B. Why does he do that?", "correct_answer": "To overcome his stuttering.", "incorrect_answers": ["In order to sound funnier.", "None of these", "Because it allows him to spit while he talks."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the nickname of Nicolas Cages character Randal Raines in the 2000 action movie Gone in 60 Seconds?", "correct_answer": "Memphis", "incorrect_answers": ["Casablanca", "Sway", "Twister"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "There are approximately 2 million sweat glands in the human body.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Selena Gomez, the star of Another Cinderella Story, also appeared in this TV show.", "correct_answer": "all of these", "incorrect_answers": ["The Suite Life of Zack  Cody", "Hannah Montana", "Wizards of Waverly Place"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What number is missing from the following sequence:  5,10,20, ___, 50, 55, 110?", "correct_answer": "25", "incorrect_answers": ["30", "40", "35"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How old is Lucy in the movie I Am Sam, when the Social Services try to take her away from Sam?", "correct_answer": "7", "incorrect_answers": ["5", "8", "6"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The so-called McBurneys point is located in this part of the human body.", "correct_answer": "Abdomen", "incorrect_answers": ["Thorax", "Foot", "Head"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the US, a record can be certified diamond, if it sells this number of copies.", "correct_answer": "10 million", "incorrect_answers": ["50 million", "5 million", "20 million"]}]